Hello hello everyone welcome to the
creative friends of the Metro channel in today's first video
we
saw portal news and indicators in front of victim of the flats as
seen in all the latest updates of gums the
market is good right now in fact along with correction
consolidation is going on a lemon
chilli some of the indicators of duty are
approaching the most important technical support levels and Nifty is again
posing a challenge at some of its long term trend resistance levels and is repeatedly replacing from there so
this volatility
can remain for a few days hence
we feel that this is the time to take a picture
approach and try to
side limit your investment whenever you get a chance keep
replying to this innovative
joint keeping this in mind which
fundamentals for office job in waiting can you
select current account which right
now I will discuss you on good valuation
on April and which questions
can you bike on, I will discuss that in this video
friends if you have not subscribed to my channel
So do it now and press the bell icon
because I keep on updating the
best of my originals on a weekly basis
and keep sharing them with you
which will be very useful for you
without a minimum of time. Let's get
started friends, as we have been doing for the last two-three
years. In today's video
also we are going to share so many staff officers
that I will not be able to give you the details of all the staff,
otherwise the video will become very
long, but those who are regular users of our channel will be
well aware of this curse because
we have definitely done the detailed review of all the staff
in some video in different pack channel lists on the channel.
Friends, in this video with
James Rate Today Price Plus, I will also give a perfect introduction
of all the staff for them with our kind love, so
that
you can get an idea of ​​what all the companies use
and why is there a missed call on all these stock numbers
for long term investment, then
when I can return to the tightening set front,
friends, today's first companies of depression,
Bajaj Finance is a very  Strong
and such a very good welcome and non-banking
finance corporation. Let's talk about 50 minutes.
It belongs to Bajaj Group and is a very
well balanced company. Its corporate
governance is good. Along with this, it is a very
mooted company. Option Dashrath
APB discussed in a different separate video in
which he talked about stocks of banking and insurance sector.
He talked about market retirement in some detail. On this,
soon
I will bring a fundamental love video. In that, we will
talk in more detail about why
Bajaj has such a mooted business.
Why is it such a stroke player in this sector?
Your brightness seems to be a good player. There seems to be
good scope for long term
investment. So, firstly, you
can maintain your price. That is
between 45,000 and 2015. Second,
if there is such a huge decline because it is affected.
Open Facebook and the
sentiments will reach 3537 and the level can also give a
very attractive price. Jabalpur long
term investment in Bajaj Finance. Now
Vikram Singh  Naukri.com, which you know is a
scam
company, is fundamentally very strong, many
businesses perform well, especially
naukri.com. Everyone must be aware of it. Then there is
99acres Mumbai portal, then there are many
startups, even in metros, you
can see a lot of jobs.
Its office from its director is
also very rapid, it can
turn on startups, many businesses have
good tech. So if you
want to activate these schools, not to manifest
potential, you can do it in the long
term group, then you will reach 40 level, this is
a good decision, you can get sector support,
where you can start depending on the minimum,
but if you should wait a little,
as you have seen, it has a lot of quality, there is a lot of
momentum in it,
as you can also see from the chart, so
if you should wait a little, then 35 and 36
will be the levels, you can tweet them. If
special efforts are made, then definitely can be a
good support level for long term
investment for which  naukri.com Next
company Mostly when we are talking about the semolina company which is
creating monopoly in India, the
market leader of its sector Nestle India
Thrasher Switzerland West companies are a
multinational company, its Indian celebs in
India, not just for a minute
you can see its
moving average on this, it is around
16 thousand to 16,000, the range of which is
very attractive, here you
can set your admission date quiz inim, if you want to wait a little, if you have a
little more conservative approach,
then you can fit the level of 15,000 to 15,000,
there admission of 20 can be
started in a very aggressive channel,
friends, next company, next step is my favorite,
such things in the banking industry,
India's largest private sector for
all India, one of the most popular
playlist all banks HDFC Bank HDFC
Bank etc. If you want to activate then I
think that 1415 sugar level can 16 part in
points  If you haven't made a solid investment, you
can definitely be facilitated.
Watch out for it. But you might want to wait a bit.
If you think that when these PHP numbers
start getting declared, there might be
some correction. Editing now could
create some pressure. Like, if all these
transporter leadership animals
start declaring their Mars Quarter Kids, then it could
become a bit problematic. So,
if you want to wait a bit, you
can tweet at the level of 1213. Differentiate there.
Thank you. Very, very strong contender for
long term investment. Next topic is
one of my favorite banks. Kotak Mahindra Bank is as fundamentally strong as
HDFC Bank. It's a
small bank for a person. And if we
talk about number plates and number of
branches and loan book, it's a
much smaller bank than this.
But still, fundamentally, it has a very strong bank.
Its corporate governance is also quite good.
So, I see the long-term interest of Kotak Mahindra Bank as important.
If you want to enroll in Kotak Mahindra Bank,
So 1718 surprise, their
son can still be in the middle of the pornographic campus, so
here you can start your enemy's
department on the college campus, you can see
support many times or see
support on two, three or four, so its
definitely a fabric starting point for
long term investment. Kotak Mahindra
Bank, but if you want to wait a little, you
can update at 1415 and a half till there, if there is a
correction because tomato pieces,
semester tractors, this bank
fundamentally does not have any vision of such a big
correction, but if the overall
investment is good,
currency pressure is created in the banking sector factor,
so if such opportunities are given to you
in the middle of all the 14-15 year festivals, then definitely can be responsible for
deployment of long term investment
capital.
China has technical companies. Next companies, Pathak
Butter, multinational company, Water India Camera,
talking about the Indian subsidiary's
business, that is the market leader, it is very
good, this is also a thick one,
along with Relax, another company I like
Pandey said that
when the market was hit by the quality of the foot segment, it was
also badly beaten, there will be a
huge decline and there has
not been much recovery from there yet.
You can see the steps, it is also around the levels of March Twenty20.
Now you can see that
in the middle of March, it was around this level,
which in today's date, for this fort, there has
not been much recovery yet and this has happened because
you would know that Bate's footwear
statement comes, this tweet comes,
along with it, there is also a shift regarding their children going to school,
so that is why since the
full alerts are not open yet, the ones which were open themselves have
also started closing again, so
due to all those factors, there is again a
problem in Bate India, after deleting it from its enemies,
there is a decline again, this is going on for about 13 to 14 years, if it is
seen anywhere around about how to be responsible, then at this time, good cause notice
to protect Bate India in
physics, if you do a test match  So the first
press love can be of 13 to 14 years,
there are many moving average
superintendents, this to and fro moving average is
around 14 and a half and
it is moving below that, so many such
stocks do
not stay below half of the morning of Women's Day for very long,
however since Bata India is also perceptible because when the
nation soldiers when
extra oil sentiments
in gas pricing, if you want to do it for 1 minute then it is
not advisable to extend the
meeting water, but if you
want to wait a little, then you can also add 12 and a half to 13 paise at any time,
if there is a little more decline, there is a
little more beating of the market, then you
can start doing extensive minutes on that occasion, but this is a very strong
company, G Road company, a good bull comment
company, it is also a motor shortage in its sector, so
after admit card net of all these things,
I see good growth potential in it for the long
time, so like this
dynasty update you can keep it
long term  Investment Next Companies
Pharmaceutical Companies But Table
Pharmaceutical Company This Left Or
Top Between Pharma Can Be Considered Average
Principal Gurmant Let us talk about the back and
that this company's product is using
very good marks regularly, it is a
company with very good market penetration,
A stop for a minute, the
first president can be stopped at 6065, its current
price is in fact quite close, a little more
correction, if you wait a little here, it
comes on this channel, then that president will
definitely be a very attractive price on that crop,
you
can start your admission there, but now if we
want to wait a little, we can update it sometime around 5055,
there it can definitely be very
attractive brother update level, the next
company is in India's lage tractor, tower
and stay celebrated, if you talk about it, then it is a
very strong player fundamentally,
from the company, it has a good market share,
it is a fat free company in the market, it is a
small cap but well managed, so it has
good growth potential, in this also
if you want to go into the travel industry,
tourism  The chairman of the industry
can be a superintending player. VIP
Industries, if you
want to start visiting, you can meet the level of 325-350. It is
very close to it,
and if a correction comes in it, then
definitely a
correction equation can be formed. So if this
pressure is only between 325-350, then
definitely you can start looking
at the best company for long term
investment. If you want to wait a little more, you have to go to
City Mall and want to keep it,
small cap can become a little difficult in this.
So if you see any such positive
between 275-300,
then definitely next in the good
price, love to talk meeting VIP
Industries from Stamford. I am talking to you about the next company
of Whirlpool, World Trade International
Company, UC Company, its Indian subsidiary
Whirlpool India.
This is also a very good strong player. It
is a debt free company, motor business has a
good market, not only air
conditioners but also in  Washing Machines, Stan
Recruitment Refrigerators For Watching This
Whirlpool India, a company that is well-positioned in the white goods sector, can try to
regulate its market by making
it your own by making it
around the twenty-20 moving average.
You can definitely make it specific
and it is around the current price table.
So if you find it tasty like this, then
definitely you will start
doubting Whirlpool India for the long term.
But if you want to wait a little bit, if
you think there might be a little more decline
in the stock, then you can paste the festival of 2006, you can make
your high
millions off there. The next companies are
Sanofi, a friend, multinational
pharmaceutical company, its Indian
States of India. We are talking on camera. To make it
one minute, the first press can be
double 75, the second 786. In such a situation, you can
wait for it, that is 7077, its
strongest definition.  It is a very good brand
in the pharmaceutical industry. Its
dividend history is very good. It
does quite well on Different. It is a good
company. It is
also very good for long term investment. Fundamentally, it is a
very soft company. There is
no need to worry if you want to invest in Different, you should
invest in it. You are going to do
more than that immediately. But
then fiber and generation companies can
also be very good for Different. All
three of them are in the pharmaceutical industry. So,
why can they be a
leading company for your defense staff selection? The
next stock is About India. About
Maintenance Pharmaceutical Company is a US
based company. Talk to its Indian subsidiary
on About India channel and
in this box also you will
see the same interesting observation. This stock is shown below its today's
moving average black alarms. If it is
below the sign on it, then
definitely an ad song top does
not remain below its 2nd day price for long. So,
definitely I think that if  This
problem seems attractive
for long term investment and definitely this is
the price channel thank you you can start
treatment for long term investment will
release your investment for long term
vision about India take off but if you want to wait a little then you
can wait for the premises of 12,500 to 13,500 if you have long
term that festival seems more attractive
if you want to wait then that
next company for India in tractor don't very from
place abhinav supervisor is
more known as brains there is no need for
me to tell much about it there is
a very
strong foot in detector it is a very good motor business
debt free business it has all its lines
where there are bheem shops which are retail
chains, they also do all the land so
they do
not need much debt there is a good increase in operations they
keep the inventory very streamlined inventory is very
fast processing due to this they are
able to give good discounts due to which
their details of customers  The base also keeps
growing in a healthy manner. Rafiq, you have
given positive updates, although it is
shown in the profit numbers, but if the remaining revenue
numbers are clear, and
they are good in that, there is a slow
recovery seen, however,
due to the quality and how the numbers are increasing, again the
contagion is visible in the stock,
but for the long term, if you
can do this alternative preparation, that is,
if you can fold this stock,
each unit can provide good
returns in the future, if you
want to start this Kwid car, then 2764
85000 price slashed price range in which
you can start explanation,
secondly you can wait for it or
keep it, but 2425 then 50,
a little more pressure is created in the stock because
of a good number of reasons to push price
seven pay commission and if at this time you can destroy
these Abhinav Supermoms, the next company
is Typing Fast related to this and
we had described it a little more detailed
when we did Best of Foreign  For those interested in investing,
Singh Meena has given
some more detailed information about Atal Quality.
If you
look at some long-term trends in Astral, it is a very good
initiative. Gaman Company is also an almost free company. It is a well-organized
garment company. If you look at the long-term trends in Astral, then you will do a lot of
written letters and
fundamentals of great value. So,
you will see very good points. On the
basis of fundamental research, if you should invest in tehsils, then you
can fit the 1550 level for 15 years. Yes, the price is
around the level, just a little more and if there is a correction in it, then decorate.
Thank you. Very strong candidate for long-
term investment on this channel. But
if you want to wait a little, then you can do 12.5 to
13 and petrol less VAT. That too is a
very good attractive price level. If
its 200 does not fall in its range, then it is
also around the 12 sugar level. So, if this
top falls to that level, it still
falls. So, definitely you can talk to your
meeting master.  Polytechnic for long term
next stock on Eicher Motors India Royal Enfield is a leading Indian company that manufactures two
wheeler motorcycles from Rs. 240 to Rs.
Royal Enfield is its brand.
It is Eicher Motors and only two wheelers.
It manufactures four wheeler commercial vehicles in
collaboration with Volvo.
Their performance and these
commercial vehicles are quite good. A
very good brand from motivational equals
Royal Enfield and many other friends of Royal Enfield.
You have many motorcycles as well as
different Galaxy series. So to
invest in Eicher Motors, I think
24 of his Black is the first attempt which was
quite attractive. Secondly, keep your preserve
register. So
one more thing from the hair is
definitely a button, very attractive price. At that
time, lifting Akshar Motors, this note is
already invested in office phone companies,
factory companies, good operations, retail
business is quite good for it and friend
request, sometimes it is motor business, so
from different I think that first year long
term potential addition motors country
true preceptor nylon and both of these  For
civil services, you feel more comfortable with these too, from
there you
can start your investment,
these companies
are currently related to the banking sector, but if I talk about the
best, friends, I have already
talked about HDFC Bank and Kotak
Mahindra Bank, both of these are my favorite banks,
but the history of Axis Bank has
not been very good, but their
current management is quite
good, Amitabh Bachchan, the Managing
Director, his history is quite good,
tastes like Brin, he did a very good job,
so I think that in the future,
Axis Bank can be promoted a little, they are
using it, it
can be a little dress, dress can be front
Vikram Thakur,
more, if I talk about four private sector banks,
if I talk about strong private sector
banks, DSC, Kotak Mahindra, Axis
Arise, these four banks seem good to me, what attracts me
in all these banks is
that feature investment, one of them is
Axis Bank, Axis Bank has seen a good improvement in its
format and time is
professional, so if you want to spend a minute, then
their near 625 675  You can tweet,
that's why these earrings can be seen around the premises, that
impression can be made by you,
that is 5 and a half to 6 bible leading company
which we will talk about is also a multi
transformer company, now see
from this side we are talking about companies for companies time,
they are in this to-do list
because for many days actually for many months there has been
consolidation going on in the pharma sector
and there is time for consolidation, there is
time for consolidation, you can complete this Muskan
stock for the fundamentals of the long
term like it will
act with Fizza, favorite one day morning, if
you see it going down a bit then
definitely dead sales and cigarette price,
second take meeting Pfizer for long term for this
quality is favorite, its first price inch
and if you want to wait a little then the second
price can be 3000, next company ABCL
is a non-banking finance company, Vote - it is the
market leader in gold finance in India,
its highest number for class at number
of customer point of view, Mannapuram Finance  A
better company than Muthoot Finance is Muthoot Finance.
After that, I will discuss
Muthoot Finance in an interesting video.
In a video, I will discuss the
currency. If you talk about its price, then there can be a
time table of 11 to 12 months where you can
start your investment calculation.
Stop that and wait a little, if the
price is between 1000 and 11, then
that too will be an attractive investment for long
term investment in the finance sector. Next,
gas distribution companies like Mahanagar Gas,
its operation is based in Mumbai and joining
Yasmin, our system operates.
Fundamentally, it is a very good company.
Rishi Prem told me that it looks good for the grocery Patel feature.
Jaswant, the operator
company, Indraprastha Gas Ltd. is a good company.
I have also talked about DSP.
In earlier videos, if we talk about cigarettes or
Pacific, then I have found Mahanagar Gas to be quite
attractive.
Its smoke is quite good as I remember. After
deducting the commission, I think it is a
special thing worth more than 1000 rupees.
If he wants to wait a little, then he
can wait for the festival of Rs 900 to 1000 and start
his personal business there and if he wants to do so, he can do it.  You
can consider Nuverus as the next company
in the general insurance sector, India's
market leader in the private sector,
ICICI Lombard. Fundamentally,
you can share your
thoughts with us about the general insurance sector. The market potential in India is a
very underrated market and its
future care needs to be taken care of. Your potential is quite good compared to its
rivals. A fundamentally sound
company in the general insurance sector in
India, ICICI Lombard, has
calculated this to arrive at the first offer price of
1314.50. The second offer price is 12.50 per share. If you
want to weigh the cross, then consider the
next companies, the
effective voltage. If we
talk about electrical and electronic manufacturing, contract manufacturing, then we are talking about Lal
's experience of 10 congressional players in India,
Addiction Technology. There was a
stock split in this, due to which the
stop went up quite high. From there, there was a
slight correction to a good level. Some
consolidation took place in the stock. So, I think if you
want to weigh a little at 3233.50, then on that table, if you  You
can also add it and start commission there. The
second price is only where
its moving average speed is 200, that is
2560 27 fourth level, if you
can update it till that trend, if it starts moving on it, then
you are seeing that for many months since the
liquid revolution,
it has supported the boys of TDS and the
maximum drop has happened, so we are talking about one and a half
movies, adventure sports and the
ODI being played in the movie is
around 369, so best for your comfort,
send new research has done in these stocks,
whichever of these two is more
suitable for the problem, flop, feel more comfortable,
you can start its 1 million there,
Agyeya company is India's leading
housing finance company HDFC Limited,
against Housing Development Finance Corporation, parent company Ford HDFC
Group, cutting side HDFC Bank, HDFC
Life in Chief Air God
Limited, from all these tent companies, that problem we are talking about
before 2425 clothes to do the minute of HDFC Limited  Attractive price,
but if you want to wait a little, you
can see its dowry movie, which is
almost in the middle of rain and strong winds, then
this tractor price will
definitely be attractive prices before the tongue, will
protect meeting for long term in
HDFC Limited, the next company is Edifice of
Management Company HDFC AMC, habitual
management companies have better complete,
I
find HDFC AMC attractive, among 2768 parts,
if you want to wait a little more, then you
can update the traffic of all 24 acquaintances, which will prove that the company for which is good
for your potential in the future, the
last company of our today's description is Maruti
Suzuki India Limited, I do
not need to tell much about it, it is the market leader
in the four-wheeler auto sector,
its market share is more than fifty percent, more than etc.
You will keep more vehicles of Maruti Suzuki on the road, then
you will know how many other designated
companies have how much market
Maruti Suzuki has a higher market share,
so the F-18 cigarette company, the four-wheeler auto
sector, tax-free companies, large companies,
very good companies for the long term. If you look at the
properties of Maruti Management, if
you
look at the long-term investment potential, then 668 and a half, that is,
1668, the price of soil can travel
very attractively. Prices will start in the range of 668.
Maruti Suzuki 800 is not already
invented, but if you want to wait a little,
you can see 060. Support was taken here many times, so
definitely a phase, that is, by bending comfortably,
that level is where you
can wait for action level. If you
see long-term potential in this, then
definitely metal price, service tax,
wicketkeeper, eyes. So, I hope
friends, we have covered many staff of digitization. This was a
short
introduction, but I hope
you will forgive me for that. There are
so many stars that
I have to add, I have given you a little introduction of all the staff
and along with that, a detailed description of their
decisions.  So
that you can keep all these stocks on your watch
and along with that their
fashions and their support separately, you can also note that down in
your mind somewhere in a diary
where you keep a note of it, you can keep
all the stocks in mind here also,
which can be maintained in the mosted
and wherever you
find nutritious, if there is some
consolidation in the market, conservation continues for some days, there is some
correction, then
you should keep an eye on the priceless support of all these stocks, keep an
eye on them and wherever you get more disease, then
you can open long term investment options
on all these stocks, you can see, but if you have seen then all these
imports, all the discussions
are your used oil that in your long term
investment, come on friends, we will start this channel on cross also,
which is Knowledge Power, the
mission of this channel is to
bring correct knowledge to you, in the coming new
videos we will discuss many interesting offices
and I will keep
bringing useful collides and topics for you  Similarly, every
Vikram will keep
discussing the market update and in the invite situation by sharing his views, so
Idli subscribe to our channel Cement Posted by
Father Felix If you like today's video content
then like the video If
you feel that this mission can help someone
then share it with your friends and family
members and
subscribe to the channel See you in the next video
and with the discussion of coffee, till then
take the institution by the